kicksusa.com 2017-07-24

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy will explain how KicksUSA collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (i.e. YOU or anyone else who enters this site) of [http://www.kicksusa.com](http://www.kicksusa.com/). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by KicksUSA.

**Personal identification information (AKA How we get your info)**

We may collect personal identification information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. You may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. But you can visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. You can always refuse to supply personally identification information, but not signing up may prevent you from entering certain parts of the site.

**Non-personal identification information (AKA what we collect your info)**

We may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer you are using and what servers and/or techno-sorcery you used to get onto the site.

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance your experience. Your web browser places cookies on your hard drive to keep a smile file on you and tell us what you are up to on our site. You can choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, some parts of the site may not work for you.

**How we use collected information (AKA what we do with what we collect)**

We might collect and use your personal information for a variety of reason:

  * **_To improve customer service_** Information you provide helps us make KicksUSA bettter for YOU, like responding to customer service requests and helping you out with whatever KicksUSA problem you have.
  * **_To personalize your experience_** The info we collect from everyone who visits this site helps us find ways to make it better, whether more user friendly or getting the product you (“you” collectively) might want
  * **_To improve our Site_** We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * **_To process payments_** We can use this info to place your orders and on the orders you told us you wanted. We won’t share this information with any third party.
  * **_To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature_** To send you things we think you might like or enjoy
  * **_To send periodic emails_** We may use the email address to send you information and updates relating to your order. The info we get may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can by contacting us via our Site.

**How we protect your information (AKA how we protect what we collected)**

We make sure all your information like your username, password, transaction info, and data are protected from any attempts to alter, access or destroy it.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and you happens over a SSL, A secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

**Sharing your personal information (who we share what we collect)**

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to anybody else. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

You may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. Also, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

KicksUSA has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We advice that you check this page frequently for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you are agreeing to this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, just don’t use our site. If you keep using our site, you’re also agreeing to accept any changes to our policy.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

KicksUSA http://www.kicksusa.com 2030 Byberry Road Philadelphia, PA 19116 kinfo@kicksusa.com

This document was last updated March 2013
